

Rifqi Finaldy

Frontend Developer

Click here to Visit my Portfolio

About Me

Experienced Frontend Developer in developing and driving projects forward from concept into production ready. Currently addicted to React and enthusiasted with Javascript. Easily inspired and prefer to keep learning and continue to challenging myself as "Skills can be taught and Personality is inherent".

Skills

- HTML
- CSS
- SASS / SCSS
- Javascript
- JQuery
- Typescript
- React JS
- Next JS

- Redux
- Custom Hook
- Tailwind CSS
- Bootstrap
- Material UI
- Styled Component
- Frammer Motion

Tools

- Figma
- Canva
- Adobe (PS, Illustrator, XD)
- Balsamia
- Contentful
- Navicat

Education

National Institute of Technology



2015 - 2020

Informatic Engineering (3.28 GPA), Head Director of Art Division of HMIF Itenas

23 Senior High School



2012 - 2015

Science Major

Training & Certificate

MyEduSolve



October 2020

Basic Graphic Design Fundamental Training.

InformIT



October 2019 - January 2020

Python (Flask) Programming Language Training to integrate with Webapp (HTML, CSS, JS).

Experience

Frontend Developer

PT. Orde Digital Intelektual (Ordent)



June 2022 - Present

- Developed web app code on 3+ app simultaneously
- Collaborated with Project Manager, System Analyst, Designer Team in concepting and analyzing concepts
- Maitaned legacy web app and bug fixing code
- Created efficient and reusable frontend system to drive web-application
- Assisted backend developer to solve the issue
- Pariticipated on project's UAT and Release
- Assited in creating technical-documentation
- Optimized 2+ web-app for maximum speed and scalability

Frontend Developer

PT. Transformasi Data Indonesia (SocketSpace)



苗 April 2021 - April 2022

- Collaborated with designer team to incorporate visual design projects into functional UI.
- Assisted in creating reusable code, components, and library for future use.
- Delivered 7+ projects of all sizes.
- Optimized user friendliness on the projects.
- Optimized SEO on 2 projects

Frontend Developer Intern Passion IT

🚞 July 2018 - September 2018

- Design & Build Dynamic Company Profile Website
- Design mockup based on user requirement
- Translate UI/UX into fully functional Code